Inventory of the Resistencia Nicaragüense records, 1983-1989
Hoover Institution Archives
- Articles and reports on Managua negotiations, 1988 May 26-28 (Folder 8: 32)
- Letter from members of Congress to Ronald Reagan, 1988 June 1 (Folder 8: 33)
- Press release, 1988 June 2 (Folder 8: 34)
- Letter from Aristides Sánchez to João Clemente Baena Soares, 1988 June 2 (Folder 8: 35)
- Statement by Enrique Bermúdez, 1988 June 3 (Folder 8: 36)
- La Prensa editorial, 1988 June 4 (Folder 8: 37)
- Letter from Directorate to Cardinal Miguel Obando y Bravo and João Clemente Baena Soares, 1988 June 4 (Folder 8: 38)
- Press releases, 1988 June 6-7 (Folder 8: 39-40)
- Transcript of press conference held by Directorate, 1988 June 7 (Folder 8: 41)
- Letter from Violeta de Chamorro to Daniel Ortega, 1988 June 7 (Folder 8: 42)
- Statement by Roberto Ferrey, 1988 June 8 (Folder 8: 43)
- Press release, 1988 June 8 (Folder 8: 44)
- Study by Stephen B. Kaplitt, 1988 June (Folder 8: 45)
- Timetable of Sandinista proposal, 1988 (Folder 8: 46)
- Transcript of press conference held by Directorate, 1988 June 8 (Folder 8: 47)
- Press release, 1988 June 8 (Folder 8: 48)
- Statement by Alfredo César, 1988 June 9 (Folder 8: 49)
- Timetable of compliance with cease fire agreement, 1988 June 9 (Folder 8: 50)
- Press release, 1988 June 24 (Folder 8: 51)
- Linder v. Calero case files, 1985-1989
  - Computer printouts of data on press reports, 1988 (Folder 9: 1-4)
  - Exhibits, 1988 (Folder 9: 5)
- Correspondence and reports used in case preparation, 1985-1989
  - 1985-1989 (Folder 10: 1-5)
  - 1986-1988 (Folder 11: 1-11)
- List of political prisoners, 1988 (Folder 12: 1)
- Text of Contadora Act, 1984 (Folder 12: 2)
- Cease fire agreement, 1989 (Folder 12: 3)
- Correspondence, 1988 (Folder 12: 4)
- Programs and proposals, 1986-1987 (Folder 12: 5)
- Reports, 1986-1988 (Folder 12: 6-7)
- Reports on investigations of attacks on civilians by Resistance commanders, 1988 (Folder 13: 1)
- Dossier on cease fire violations, 1988 (Folder 13: 2)
- Correspondence, clippings, and reports, 1986-1990 (Folder 13: 3-7)
- Report on diplomacy by Unidad Nicaragüense Opositora, 1986 (Folder 14: 1)
- Correspondence, clippings, and reports, 1985-1989 (Folder 14: 2-6)
- Report on education in Nicaragua, 1986 (Folder 15: 1)
- Telex messages, 1986-1987 (Folder 15: 2)
- Correspondence, clippings, and reports, 1985-1989 (Folder 15: 3-7)
- Report on human rights in Nicaragua, 1985 (Folder 16: 1)
- Press releases and reports on Managua negotiations, 1988 June 7-9 (Folder 16: 2)
- Law on electoral reform, 1989 April 15 (Folder 16: 3)
- Proposals on electoral reform presented by opposition, 1989 March 31 (Folder 16: 4)
- Law on communications media, 1989 April 15 (Folder 16: 5)
- Financial records of the Nicaraguan-American National Foundation, 1989 (Folder 16: 6)
- Correspondence, clippings, and reports, 1985-1990 (Folder 16: 7-9)
- Press releases, 1988 (Folder 17: 1)
- Clippings, 1986 (Folder 17: 2)
- Correspondence and reports, 1986-1988 (Folder 17: 3-8)
- Clippings, 1985-1986 (Folder 18: 1)
- Memoranda and reports, 1985-1986 (Folder 18: 2)
- Correspondence and reports, 1986-1988 (Folder 18: 3-7)
- Requests for asylum made to the United States Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1989-1990 (Folder 19: 1-6)
- Correspondence and memoranda, 1987-1988 (Folder 19: 7)
- Clippings, 1986-1989 (Folder 20: 1)
- Agendas for meetings, 1985-1989 (Folder 20: 2)
- Correspondence, proposals, and reports, 1986-1989 (Folder 20: 3-8)
- Clippings, 1985-1986 (Folder 21: 1)
- Bulletins and serial issues, 1985-1986 (Folder 21: 2)
- Correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 1985-1987 (Folder 21: 3-8)
- Reports, 1986 (Folder 22: 1-2)
- Correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 1985-1989 (Folder 22: 3-7)
- Clippings, 1986 (Folder 23: 1)
- Reports, 1983-1988 (Folder 23: 2)
- Correspondence, memoranda, press releases, and reports, 1985-1989 (Folder 23: 3-7)
- Clippings, 1983-1986 (Folder 24: 1-4)
- Bulletins, 1986 (Folder 24: 5)
- Correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 1985-1986 (Folder 24: 6-8)
- Photographs, 1985-1986 (Folder 25: 1-2)
- Report on Nicaragua War Handicapped Project, 1987 (Folder 25: 3)
- Bulletins and serial issue, 1983-1986 (Folder 25: 4)
- Correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 1986-1989 (Folder 25: 5-9)
- Chronology, 1987-1988 (Folder 25: 10)
- Clippings, 1989 (Folder 26: 1)
- Requests for asylum made to the United States Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1989 (Folder 26: 2-3)
- Minutes of meetings held by the directors of Unidad Nicaragüense Opositora, 1985-1987 (Folder 26: 4-7)
- Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Folder 26: 8-9)
- Lists of ex-National Guard prisoners, 1989 (Folder 26: 10)
- Clippings, 1985-1986 (Folder 27: 1)
- List of disappeared persons, 1988 (Folder 27: 2)
- Paper by Curtin Winsor, Jr., 1986 (Folder 27: 3)
- Patriotic agreement, 1986 (Folder 27: 4)
- Press releases and communiqués, 1985-1989 (Folder 27: 5-9)
- Records of expenses, 1986 (Folder 27: 10)
- Correspondence, memoranda, and reports, 1986-1989 (Folder 27: 11-12)
- CLOSED (Folder 28)